my
[Music]
hello
[Applause]
and hopefully sign him up
and i call myself here as a teacher of
life okay so
to help me
welcome you all may i introduce to you
the theme of this uh
the leader the captain of the
ship of this team
none other than
mr and bill
you know
[Laughter]
thank you
are you really here are you
convinced
thank
you honesty you're used you used to know
about fwd
fwd
and meaning
that nangalito classic amazing
opportunity with
chickens
so there are many people like
a farmer you got a
[Music]
and the rest of us who are passionately
inviting people
donald need farmer you know amazing
opportunity with fwd now
this farmer is a financial wealth
plumber producer
[Music]
20 and more people earning six to seven
teachers again yeah another
is a politician a congressman
who happened nasa wanna billion dollar
round table
[Music]
foreign
then lastly
is this
70 year old
lady okay now this
shout out is how can i
give back
okay so again whatever your category
accident and terrorism coverage for 500
000 pesos
this is 1799
for one year
inch
okay
so you could send the link your special
link to your friends to your relatives
guide nasa
uh the garcia lesson
okay
happy birthday
[Music]
this is a traditional life glance
that can able to give you three times
critical illness comfort
okay
being critical illness major
no
uh the diagnosis you are issued of one
million
a diagnosed can on cancer
okay fwt will give you one billion
but
you don't need to pay any more of the
premium
still insured of two remaining major
critical illness
until age 75 healthy
there there is a healthy life benefit
100 percent annual healthy life benefit
at age 17 70
the fwd new premium
so that's
fwd set for help
okay another is the set for tomorrow
term insurance only term insurance name
[Music]
plus 1 million for the white so that's
total of 2 million pesos
so only in fwd so those are some of the
many
products
okay so
that's
fwd are very
uh dependable
okay
partners
if you will decide to join us here in
mountain
of fwd
of solid experience in providing
financial services says
summit club qualifier in switzerland
electric qualifier for manager
silver level attack unit manager
founding president of his own journey
foundation
because of this business president of
her rp truck carrier foundation
jojo josephine
one two three
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for coming
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
happy birthday
thank you thank you so much for coming
over and celebrate the special day of
our vm jojo thank you
foreign
is
guys i'm very excited
yes
very excited
[Music]
good luck